there's a lot of terrible things going on in the world right now we know that i want to talk
about this america's missed out model next time model documentary that's what i want to talk about
okay because i'm trying to understand these these people i'm trying to understand how you thought
you was gonna quit your best friend show with an email and that that would be acceptable you see
anytime anytime i'm watching nonsense like this i'm gonna try and find a way to take it to be
useful in a in a higher vibrational way of things so so so let's just talk about communication y'all
i need y'all to understand something that a lot of times people will say i have a communication
problem i'm not good at communication when it's really not about that you're not good at
communication it's that you are insecure or you are avoidant the issue isn't communication
like you know how to communicate you just don't know how to communicate when you are a scared when
you are scared of the outcome that's not about having a that's not about not knowing how to
communicate that's about not knowing how to come how to confront difficult situations so
you are on a show for eight seasons with your bff and your method of quitting is an email
nigga i wouldn't talk to your ass no more neither and he said it was the longest three days of my life
you had three days to be like you know what let me call her and you didn't
child child like how how and tyra is out of her cotton picking mind on on this documentary at least
however like what kind of best friend is y'all he said we had a relationship we had a relationship
i don't even remember what my comment on butchware's page on butchware's um video was
i just know that that video was stupid um i'm watching this show and i'm seeing a lot of
just my own experiences too because they're really like you should be able to handle yourself
you should be able to handle when things go left you should be able to handle yourself you
shouldn't have to expect the producers to handle it and i remember when i was on insecure and i was
like you know you're telling isa like your publicist is wilding and being disrespectful and she was like
that's not my business and the thing about it is that when you're in those scenarios like you are
someone's employee so it is your business you know i mean and later once she also like said
publicly that when sorry later she publicly repeated the exact same story so people understood that i was
not exacerbating i was not exaggerating etc like it was all the same then folks was like oh
um yeah that was your business so like when you are working that is not in my opinion so this is for
anyone who wants to be in tv production if you want people to come on set and you want them to have no
opinions and have no just be a subject then baby you better protect them you better protect them
if they're not going to have a voice if they're not going to have input if they're if you literally
just want them to be a subject who goes on set you know whether you're a model or an actor etc etc
and and and and that's the vibe then you know that you are responsible and i have definitely had
producers act like if you're not my responsibility the hell i'm not the hell i'm not i did not realize
how they were body like shaming folks on this show and i know people are like yeah but that was the
time no mean has always been mean you feel me the term body shaming is some new shit mean has always
been mean she got a wide booty is mean she need to lose 150 pounds when the girl's 150 pounds is mean
now i ain't saying i'm an easy person to work for but that's some mean shit i i i i i i ain't never
been mean not not this kind of way and then they said that that video where tyra said i'm rooting for
you that she had said some other shit and i thought that was the video but then i'm like of course it's
not the video because they it's an edit the way that you all have the way that you all think that
butch ware is gonna win a governor like i i think it's literally delusional and insane for you all to
think that butch ware is going to do an upset for the state of california for the governorship of the
state of california that means that you all think that voting on a governor level is fair for the state
of california which has the fourth highest gdp okay the fourth highest gross domestic product
in the world in the world what where y'all where where y'all at
where where y'all at you talking about the no kings protest it shouldn't even be called a protest it's
not a protest there are no kings so what are you protesting there are no kings none of these people
are called kings so you're literally not protesting anything there are fascists we have authoritarian
rule hold up butch ware is transphobic lord lord i didn't know that i didn't know that
no king should just be a vision board party because that's really what it is i didn't know that
somebody i what did he say that was transphobic chili from tlc is maga chili from tlc is
yeah i've known chili was on another wave when she had her show nick cannon is a trump supporter
what what what you said nicholas well democrats are the kkk oh nick chili donated money
to trump is it the drugs are people on drugs i wish people would stop calling me a celebrity
because i'm i really don't exist in any shape way or form like these people chili always been weird
she got mad when people called her chocolate did she really i knew she was weird when she had the
list of things that a nigga had to be to be with her and then she was with a man a white man
he did an interview with amber rose i'm about to take my nyquil and shut it down
democrats don't like black people but republicans do they do like black people they like using them
she says she's not chocolate she's caramel i wouldn't say she's chocolate either but
she's more like a hazelnut like a nutella no i don't roll up nick cannon said trump okay this is why i
don't like when people say like don't listen to celebrities under my posts because
like the celebrities that y'all are talking about are not scholars
like i'm i'm a scholar like i've gone to school i've written essays i've written books
i'm a scholar i am respected by other scholars so when people be like don't listen to anything
from amanda seals i'm like and they're like because she's a celebrity i'm like
i'm not talking about my ass i'm talking from the like the work here goes the colorism where where
where where's the colorism at where the colorism at she's not chocolate she's hazelnut
that's not colorism that's color wheel color wheeling i'm an actual painter like that's not chocolate
right there it's hazelnut i painted that that color right there i think that's burnt yeah that's
burnt sienna with a little bit of red ochre in it okay so y'all love to call colorism just
addressing a skin tone when if you were gonna paint that person you know hazelnut is a shade of
chocolate but no one means hazelnut when they say chocolate and you know that so let's cut it out
let's really stop with the with the nonsense you know when people call somebody chocolate they're
referring to the rich dark chocolate like this organic dark chocolate from grenada
uh that's what they're referring to when they say chocolate okay let's let's quit let's like just
act like what it is but her be offended by it now that's a whole other thing it's one thing to be
like i'm not chocolate i wish i was i feel like i'm more hazelnut see someone posted that if kamala
was president we'd be at brunch i want to fight them cop and a half was on tv the other day i'm gonna get a
check for 25 cents i'm gonna go to check for 25 cents um anyways i really just popped on here
because i just needed to vent and y'all be here waiting for ventilations but i'm just watching
these people and they are so tone deaf with themselves and you're just like huh y'all y'all
really missing it you know and if i'm quite honest with you butch is missing it too butch
where did an entire video about how nobody supported him who were socialists and to be quite honest
in my opinion the way that people should be supporting you should be based on your actions
not by your label so i feel like if it was like you should support me because i've done x y z
a b c three to the seventh power that's one thing however you should support me because i called you
and asked you to that's that's what i mean by it's still politics you're still operating in the
politics of it all which is everyone just clicking up and i'll tell you what i told him which is like
okay but like what are like what are you doing in terms of constituency services because in socialism
the material conditions are what calls for the party so the people are make who are who make the
demand for the party so you know if you're if you're looking at governorships if you're looking at
you know people who are running for office in any places that you are where where elections are
actually fair the question to me becomes how are you filling a gap created by the position that you are
actually uh running for uh running for so like i want to know if someone's running for governor what
are you doing to fill the gap what are you doing to fill the gaps that the current governorship
policies are creating what are you already doing to fill the gaps what are you already doing
to fill the gaps that the governorship policies have created because getting into office is not when
change starts and it's not when it should start you should already before you run for office be
attacking in real time that which you are going to be able to shift exponentially when you're in office
the in office should be the cherry on top the in office should be man if i was just in office then we
could do this xyz the voting should be the last part here in the united states you have been tricked into
believing that the voting is the first part it's not the black panther party for self-defense is how it
started they did not start with a direction of politics in terms of being in in politics they started
with a direction of addressing the gaps that politics had created and self-defense is not just
like self-defense with guns because we know that the people have been weaponized like we know that
policy has been weaponized against the people in a myriad of ways housing medical etc so the party of
self-defense is that no i don't see myself aiding him and filling those gaps i don't live in california
and i don't need to aid him in filling those gaps i do what i do i'm not an organizer there are several
many many organizers and i don't even know why you are asking me what my responsibility is to butch wear
i don't have any responsibility to butch wear anyone who wants to run for office
should be filling the gaps that they are running for office to change period period one of the reasons
why brandon johnson is so successful in ball in baltimore is because he was already doing the work
that he then became mayor to expound upon so even if it's not your um even if you are not necessarily
organizing on the ground as like a specific about a specific policy you at the very least need to be
creating coalition for the organizers there there has to be a value that you're already adding
and if you notice most of these people are not a value add they were lawyers they were professors
they were bankers they were already rich when you look at majority of the politicians that end up in
positions outside of local government they were snatched up by you know these like election committees
that come and find people that they think can win that they feel like are already in a position
to win and that they can control the literal current prime minister of grenada was a lawyer
huh so why is a public servant
going it how so why is what's the role is supposed to be a public servant yet you are putting people in
position who are further from the public than anybody else it's not like they're criminal defense
attorneys nine times out of ten they're either da's or they work in the private sector jasmine
jasmine crock getting no organizer she was an attorney getting six figures a year so you know when i when i
see this and let me also just add i'm just having this as even a rhetorical conversation because to be
quite honest i don't think any of this shit is going to work and if it ain't about revolution i really
don't want to hear about it all this we need a third party and blah blah blah is really just code
for i'm not really ready for this to end because i don't have any idea what could come next
because i haven't actually been a part of building what could come next and all i do every day is try
to help people's brains open up so that they can be a part of the work that's already being done
to establish something for the next every time i hear y'all talk about we need a third party all i
hear is i'm afraid of actually burning this shit down that's all i hear i'm afraid of actually seeing
change i done just came back from cuba these niggas had an entire revolution i am from grenada
them niggas had an entire revolution they stood up to imperialism an island of 110 000 people said
we are going to stand against imperialism and did so for four years you know how long four years is
and robin right here has got it right she said this is not a system that can be meaningfully changed
from the inside no nobody has ever changed this system from the inside so when i hear people who
claim to be leftist being like i'm running for office i look at them hella sideways because that
means that they have a jesus complex at best that's the best case scenario i have a jesus because i saw
somebody you know who i think is a really solid public servant say to me well you know i'm running
for office i said why they were running for senate i said why she said well because i want to stand for
my children i want to give my children a chance and that i'm like no do you think that you as an
individual can go in there and shake it up that's the other part i don't see no coalition all the
leftists who want to try to shake shit up should be running together or should be running i should say
concurrently in all of the states that have the opportunity to do so they should be a tag team
none of this shit should be disorganized which is how i know that it's not really about being leftist
well maybe it is that's why it's disorganized like this is kb right here it's from the inside
how they're able to influence the minds of those who think they can change from the inside i don't
even know what that means actually so i'm not even gonna go deal with that so all i'm saying is
um i tried i tried to make it make sense it didn't make sense so and it's too late and i don't feel well
so i had to just let it go um someone asked me what this revolution looked like to me
i wouldn't even talk about that on here k like the fly do you even know me they miss me and love me
that's very scary people tell people love to talk about the civil rights movement
we were organized and had strategies people love to talk about the civil rights movement we were
organized and strategies first of all them niggas was fighting every motherfucking day
during the civil rights movement okay them niggas was arguing and fighting and and and there was all
type from there was all type of um you know ego shit ego trip crap going on what don't don't don't
don't get romanticized now see ogandala said ogandala 1948 said yes we were now i'm assuming ogandala was
born in 1948 okay and she's telling you i was there y'all be thinking the niggas was sitting
around at barbecues like we gonna get these whites no there's always been tokens there's always been
a really good book to read is like um some good books that i feel like really give you some insight
into the civil rights movement like force and freedom by um kelly carter jackson actually no
force of freedom is about the abolitionist movement her second book um i'm so tired uh her second book
though is about that um and also it's good to read john lewis's um memoir john lewis's memoir john
lewis's memoir which i can't remember either mind you i've read both these books
um but they'll keep it 100 with you and you really realize like oh
hey kimmy oh these people's this was there was always arguing yes you said the drewski person
that's hilarious no his his book is not called good trouble his book is called like
something with the wind the graphic novel is different i'm talking about his memoir and it's
big as hell you you too late non-vin me we already talked about that so anyway those are my thoughts
um and uh for anybody who wants to say things like we can't see a revolution it'll never happen
i'm so glad that you wasn't around for the french revolution for the haitian revolution for the grenada
revolution for the cuban revolution for the the uh zapatista um movement for walking with the wind
thank you mimi for the um for don's rebellion for nat turner rebellion i'm so glad you wasn't there
i'm so glad that's me naming them shits off top of my head i can't even remember books that i've read
think about how many there are y'all need to realize that you have been put under psychological
operation and get your shit together and i love how folks are like well they didn't trust the
government for a vaccine but they trust the government for elections to to choose when to
go to war etc i'm like are y'all out of your damn minds why are you trusting the government at all
for anything at any time like this government has never showed you that it cares about you ever
it ain't got no programs that care about you it it it like never never so
you know when i see y'all talk about like elections i'd be like baby
they have interfered in elections in damn near every country across the world
why do you think they're not interfering in ours why why do you think that your vote is being counted
that's just a weird and then you got these folks who tell you if voting didn't matter
they wouldn't work so hard to stop you from doing it that's absolutely not true first of all these
people hate you it's just enough to give you a hard time i love how there's like a logic that's applied
to people who are literal psychotic irrational people there doesn't have to be a logic to them
not wanting you to vote they don't want you to vote because they don't like you that's why they
don't want you to vote and not getting you to vote preventing you from vote gives them something to
do it actually like busies their hands we got to get less niggers to vote so now y'all got some jobs
it's like it's like what how are you trying to apply rationale to people who have demonstrated
over and over and over again that they are irrational these people are irrational they're
judging you off of your melanin count and then when people say yes these are the rights my ancestors
fought for no that is not accurate either you're right your ancestors already had these rights
this was one of the ways they were demonstrating to the united states that they are playing in their face
and it went on for decades
so that's why you have voting rights happening at the same time as freedom rights happening at the same time as
lunch counter sit-ins happening because these were all ways that they were being disenfranchised
in the states due to states laws even though the federal law which is supposed to supersede the states law
says that no u.s citizen this is this 14th amendment that no u.s citizen should be denied rights that's what
they were fighting for to to be like hey y'all has said so like what the hell so to me to be like
i'm gonna continue to participate in this establishment
because my grant my ancestors fought for this establishment to let them pretend to participate
is nuts thank you mike micris i mean your in-law supports trump rather than our fellow immigrants
i hope they come for your in-law and get him right on out of there i made the shirt you can get your
they did not you can get your we cannot vote our way out of evil shirt at amandalandexports.com
okay i'm going to sleep so that's my ted talk for tonight um for the record i'm never gonna bring
up chili again because i don't care voting is not a tool i don't know why you fully believe that
there is nothing that it has been shown to you is useful so you fully believing that voting is a tool
makes zero sense and is a demonstration of you fully being indoctrinated
how has voting ever been useful to you let me take my eyes to sleep let me take my nyquil
night y'all
you